<resources>
    <string name="app_name">lab5ex2</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="Ch1Text">Chapter 1: The Whispering Forest\n\nThe sun hung low in the sky, casting long shadows over the dense forest. At first glance, it appeared like any other forest—tall trees with thick trunks, their leaves rustling gently in the wind. But if you listened closely, there was something different. A soft murmur seemed to travel on the breeze, as if the trees themselves were whispering secrets.\n\nElena had been warned about the Whispering Forest ever since she was a child. Her grandmother used to tell her stories of the spirits that lived within the woods—spirits that could guide, but also deceive. As a young girl, Elena had dismissed the stories as nothing more than fantasy. But as she stood at the edge of the forest now, feeling the cool wind against her skin, something inside her told her that there was more truth to those tales than she had ever realized.\n\nHer heart raced as she stepped into the shadow of the trees. The forest seemed to close in around her, the trunks rising like silent sentinels. The whispers grew louder now, though no words could be made out. The path before her twisted and turned, the way forward uncertain.\n\n\'Stay on the path,\' her grandmother’s voice echoed in her mind, the warning that had always stayed with her.\n\nBut the path ahead was narrow and winding, barely visible through the undergrowth. Elena hesitated for a moment before stepping forward. She wasn’t sure what she was looking for, but she knew she had to keep going. The forest was calling to her.\n\nAs she walked deeper into the woods, the air grew colder, the whispers more urgent. Suddenly, the trees parted, revealing a clearing bathed in soft, golden light. At the center stood an ancient stone archway, covered in ivy and moss. It was unlike anything Elena had ever seen before—an entrance to something beyond.\n\nShe took a deep breath, her pulse quickening. There was no turning back now.</string>
</resources>